《致命女人》前情提要
Previously on Why Women Kill...
你可以随心所欲绿你妻子
You can cheat on your wife all you want,
但是休想碰我妻子
but you're not touching mine.
我爱上你了
I am in love with you.
你知道规则的  我永远不会
You knew the rules. I will never...
离开我妻子
leave my wife.
我能感觉到罗伯还在生那晚的气
So I can tell Rob is still mad about the other night.
他已经多日没打给我了
He hasn't called in days.
要是他和她在一起那么幸福  为什么还要跟我在一起
Why would he even be with me if he was so happy with her?
或许她做了什么伤害他
Maybe she did something to hurt him
他需要时间去原谅她
and he needs time to forgive her.
我在忙的那个项目
This project I've been involved with,
快完成了  我会晚上准时回来吃饭  每晚都是
it's almost over. I'll be home in time for dinner. Every night.
是赫克托
It's Hector.
他是我有过的最好的理发师
He was the best hairdresser I ever had.
卡尔的轻率之举我已经耳闻一段时间了
I've known for some time about Karl's indiscretions.
我看到他的车停在某个三流旅馆
I saw his car parked at some seedy motel.
你到底是怎么想的
What in God's name?
我们很久没见过面了
We haven't seen each other in years.
只有赫克托
Hector was the only person
能看清我真实的为人
who ever saw me for the man I truly am.
别再浪漫化你肮脏的一时放纵
Stop romanticizing your grubby little fling.
你爱他吗
Do you love him?
爱
I do.
你睡着了
You fell asleep.
吃掉它
Take this.
我觉得我不应该吃
I don't think I should.
我不在的时候  你们俩是不是睡了
While I was away, did you two fuck?
我们绝对睡了
We absolutely fucked.
好吧
Okay.
这是注定要发生的  对吧
This was bound to happen, right?
既然我们都住在一起了
Since we're all together now.
我们来谈谈我的剧本吧
All right, let's talk about my script.
我估计出价能有六位数  接近一百万
I'm expecting offers in the high six-figure range.
好好待洁德  她是你的灵感女神
Be good to Jade. She's your muse.
他的灵感女神
His muse?
过去两年  收拾烂摊子的人是我
I am the one who spent the last two years
收拾烂摊子的人是我
cleaning up the mess he made of our lives.
-他干什么了  -他什么没干
- What did he do? - What didn't he do?
安非他命  可卡因
Speed, cocaine.
他是个瘾君子
He's an addict.
制片人之一想要我改写
One of the producers wants a rewrite.
如果我可以按时把作品交上去的话  我就能回归
And if I can get it to them on time, then... I'm back.
然后就会有收入了  洁德  我就可以照顾你了
And the money that will follow, Jade, I can take care of you.
致命女人
第一季 第七集
*月亮发着红光*
* The moon was all aglow *
*但你眼里是天堂*
* But heaven was in your eyes *
*你告诉我*
* The night that you told me *
*善意谎言的那晚*
* All those little white lies *
*星星似乎都知道*
* The stars all seemed to know *
*你不是真心叹气*
* You didn't mean all those sighs *
*你告诉我*
* The day that you told me... *
那个叫艾普尔的女孩在1号线上
That girl April is on line one.
跟她说我在开会
Tell her I'm in a meeting.
*善意谎言的那天*
* All those little white lies *
*谁会不相信那嘴唇*
* Who wouldn't believe those lips *
*谁会不相信那眼睛*
Who wouldn't believe those eyes
*你告诉我*
The night that you told me
你昨晚很晚才回来
You were out late last night.
你和谁在一起
Who were you with?
就是田径队里的一些朋友
Just some of the guys from the track team.
*善意谎言的那晚*
All those little white lies
*恶魔在你心中*
The devil was in your heart
*但你眼里是天堂*
But heaven was in your eyes
*你告诉我*
The time that you told me
伊莱  你这么早出来干什么
Eli, what are you doing out so early?
我去慢跑
Oh, just going for a jog.
*善意谎言的那次*
All those little white lies
*那些*
All those
*善意*
Little white
*谎言*
Lies...
你能帮我按铃吗  夫人
So, can you ring me up for that, ma'am?
贝瑟妮
Bethany.
谢谢你来见我
Thank you for meeting me.
嗯  我...  收到你的短信我有点意外
Yeah. I was... I was a little surprised to get your text.
有段时间没联系过了
It's, um, it's been a minute.
是啊  我很抱歉
Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry about that.
我知道我之前消失了
I know I kind of disappeared there.
我还以为你找到别人了
Yeah. Thought maybe you had, uh, found someone else.
不不  不是那样的  我...
No, no, nothing like that. I just, you know...
暂时从良了
Took a different path for a while.
-对  对  -嗯
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
好了  谭雅
All right, Tanya,
听我的
listen to me.
你去和你朋友玩
You're gonna go play with your friends
妈妈要和朋友谈话  好吗
while Mommy talks to her friend, okay?
-好  -乖乖
- Okay. - Oh, big girl.
他们在游乐场  快去
I see them on the playground. You better go.
天呐
Oh, my God.
她个头好大
She's so big.
-是啊  -我印象中她还是个婴儿
- I know. - In my head, I still think of her as a baby.
-在小孩世界里  24个月就像是一生  -嗯
- Yeah, well, 24 months is like a lifetime in kid-years. - Yeah.
这是我从墨西哥搞到的
Okay, so I got this shit from Mexico.
掺了点东西  不过质量还是很好
It's stepped on a little bit, but it's good.
就加了15%的婴儿泻药
Just, like, 15% baby laxatives.
绝对能让你嗨
It'll definitely get you high.
但这玩意儿
But this shit
是从哥伦比亚海运过来的
just fell off the back of a fucking boat from Colombia.
我只是将它切开  打包
Okay, all I did was chop it up and bag it,
我发誓  伊莱
and I swear to God, Eli,
你一打开  你的整张脸就会麻痹掉
the second you open it, your entire face goes numb.
多少钱
Okay, how much?
3.5克三百块
Give you an eight ball for 300?
你买两份的话  我可以五百卖你
Or I can do two for five.
不过这是我能开出的最大折扣了
That's the best I can do, though.
我想给谭雅的大学基金存钱
I'm trying to save for Tanya's college fund.
你是个好妈妈
Well, you're a good mom.
好  我要两份
All right, I'll take two.
好
Okay.
很开心你回来了
Nice to have you back.
卡尔
Karl.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
该死  现在才早上7点
Bloody hell, it's 7:00 in the morning.
我昨晚很生你气
I was so angry with you last night.
你跟我说话的方式
The way you spoke to me.
听着  萨蒙妮
Look, Simone...
我整晚没睡一直在想
I was up all night thinking to myself,
真希望自己没跟那个男人结婚
"I wish I'd never married that man.
他偷走了我生命中这十年的时光
He's stolen the last ten years of my life."
好吧  抱歉
All right, I'm sorry.
给  穿上
Here, put that on.
为什么
Why?
快点穿吧
Just do it.
行
All right.
然后我开始想我们在一起共度的时光
Then I started thinking about our time together.
你教我怎么滑雪
You taught me how to ski...
怎么跳探戈
...how to tango.
怎么说法语
Hmm. How to speak French.
学会怎么再要一杯霞多丽可不算说法语
Asking for more chardonnay is not really speaking French.
最重要的是
Most importantly,
你教会我怎么自嘲
you taught me how to laugh at myself.
事实上  你没有偷走我的任何东西
The truth is, you haven't stolen anything from me.
如果有的话
If anything,
你给我的远远超过了我应得的
you've given me more than I deserved.
很抱歉  我快被你吊胃口到烦死了
I'm sorry, the suspense is slightly killing me now.
你到底要说什么
Where is this going?
跟我来
Follow me.
说清楚  我还是觉得我们该离婚
Just to be clear, I still think we should get a divorce.
我猜也是
Uh, yes, I assumed as much.
但是就因为你不能做我的丈夫
But just because I can't have you as a husband
不代表你不能做我的朋友
doesn't mean I can't have you as a friend.
我是喜欢让自己的朋友开心快乐的
And I do like to keep my friends happy.
赫克托
Hector.
你好  卡尔
Hello, Karl.
我从未比此刻更加爱你
I have never loved you more than I do in this moment.
拜托卡尔  别当着你男友秀恩爱
Please, Karl, not in front of the boyfriend.
你好
Hello.
希拉
Sheila.
你的公寓管理员跟我说你在这里
Your apartment manager told me you were down here.
我希望能跟你吃个午饭
I was hoping we could get lunch.
抱歉  餐厅打电话让我去上班
Sorry, I just got called into work.
两个侍应生病了
Two waitresses are sick.
我得把制服洗干净然后去格伦代尔
I have to clean my uniform and get over to Glendale.
没关系  我们改天再聊
It's fine. We can catch up another time.
确实有很多需要聊的
Well, there's certainly a lot to catch up on.
发生什么事了吗
Has something happened?
佩尔斯基夫人
Mrs. Persky...
请你离开一下
I need you to leave.
为何
Why?
我得跟朋友聊聊
I need to talk to my friend.
聊什么
What about?
这是私事
It's private.
关于性的  是吧
So sex, huh?
赶紧走吧
Just go!
你好像很烦躁
You seem irritable.
罗伯甩了我
Rob dumped me.
是吗
He did?
他送来了玫瑰花  附了一张便条
Yeah, he sent roses with a note
写着  "我不能再见你了  请原谅我"
saying, "I can't keep seeing you, please forgive me."
好吧  你知道总会有这么一天的
Oh, well, you knew this day was coming.
是啊  我以为他会像个男人一样
Yeah. I just thought he would be man enough
跟我当面说的
to tell me to my face.
我昨天给他工作的地方打了十次电话
You know, I phoned him at his work yesterday ten times.
他的秘书克莱尔不给我转接
His secretary, Claire, won't put me through.
亲爱的  是时候该向前看了
Well, honey, it is time to move on.
你也不想自讨没趣吧
You don't want to embarrass yourself. Well--
是的
Yeah.
你又回来干什么
What are you doing back here?
我带了我丈夫来
I brought my husband.
我想让他看看你是怎么跟我说话的
I want him to see how you talk to me.
我该走了  晚点联系你
I should go. I'll call you later.
-谢谢  -抱歉
- Thanks. - Sorry...
怎么拉着一张脸
Aw, why the long face?
你的那位甩了你吗
Did your fella dump you?
你妻子真的是个很差劲的人  你知道吗
Your wife is a horrible person. Do you know that?
是的  我知道
Yeah, I'm aware.
我以为我们很为这个出价而高兴呢
I thought we were excited about the offer.
不  不是
No, no.
听着  我当然相信你
Look, of-of course I trust you.
嗯  你做你的专业事  很好
Yeah. I mean, do your thing. Okay.
好吧  再见
All right, bye.
该死
Oh, shit.
一切可好
Is everything all right?
是的
Hey. Uh, yes.
已经有人出价买我的剧本
Yeah, there's-there's an offer on the table for the script.
但是拉马尔想再等等更高出价
But Lamar wants to hold out for more money,
你知道这让我觉得很紧张
which, you know, makes me kind of nervous.
你又吃了什么药
What are you on right now?
什么  我没有
What? Nothing.
是吗  那这是什么动作
Oh, yeah? Then what's this, then?
今年的花粉非常厉害
It-it... it's a heavy pollen year.
伙计
Dude...
都上新闻了
It's been on the news.
我们是一条船上的蚂蚱
We are on the same team.
如果你要犯傻我也救不了你
I cannot cover for you if you're gonna be stupid about it.
好吧  很抱歉
All right, I'm sorry.
阿得拉对我来说已经没效果了
The addy wasn't cutting it for me anymore,
所以我需要点药效更强的东西
so I just-- I needed something a little bit stronger.
为什么  剧本都写完了
Why? The script is done.
你们在哪
Guys?
我们在这里
Yeah, we're in here.
别拿手弄鼻子
Get your hand out of your face.
-好吧  -抱歉
- All right. - Sorry.
我得跟你们俩谈谈
I need to talk to you both.
-好的  你想谈什么  -听着
- Yeah, what's on your mind? - Look,
我知道我说过对你们俩的事情我不计较
I know I said I was okay with what went on with you two,
但显然我是计较的
but clearly, I wasn't.
我感觉自己只走了一晚上
I felt like I went away for the night,
你们就突然组成了一个没有我的小队
and you two had suddenly become this little team without me.
我知道指责你们并不公平
And it's not fair to blame you,
因为是我当初让咱们三个走到一起的
because I'm the reason we're all together in the first place.
我只是觉得在不知道会如何发展的情况下
I just feel like I talked you into this
我劝你们加入了这段关系
with absolutely no idea of how we would make it work.
没事
Well, that's okay.
-我们可以想出办法的  -是的
- Yeah. I mean, we will figure it out. - We will.
但是我们需要一些帮助
But we're gonna need some help,
我已经找好了一个开始的地方
and I think I found just the place to start.
爱  令人快乐的活动[限定]
爱越多越好活动股份有限公司
"L'Amour the Merrier Events, Limited"?
活动
Events?
你想让我们去参加群P吗
You want us to go to an orgy?
不算是群P
Oh, it's not an orgy.
就是个多角情爱的活动
It's a polyamory retreat.
这不就是"群P"的委婉说法吗
Isn't that just a fancy way of saying "Orgy"?
别再说群P了
Stop saying orgy.
好吧
All right.
这是一个在圣地亚哥的酒店为期三天的活动
This is a three-day event at a hotel in San Diego.
他们有研讨会和讲座
They have workshops, lectures,
旨在帮助
all designed to help people
那些刚接触多角恋生活方式的人
who are new to the polyamorous lifestyle.
整个活动都是由那些知道如何
The whole thing is designed by experts who know
让我们这种关系正常运转的专家设计的
how to make a relationship like ours work.
看  这是其中一个研讨会
Oh, look, so here's one of the seminars.
"协商界限和
"Negotiating Boundaries and
多角恋关系协议"
Polyamorous Relationship Agreements."
听起来挺有帮助的对吧
Doesn't that sound helpful?
对  挺有帮助的
Yeah, it really does.
-让我看看  -看到了吧
- Um, let me-- let me see. - See?
那么我就去预定了
So, I'll go make the reservations.
-我们明天就出发  -好的
- We'll leave tomorrow. - All right.
-太好了  -好的  没问题
- Yeah, wonderful. - Yeah. Yep.
你没事吧  宝贝
You okay, babe?
没事没事  就是有点过敏
Yeah, yeah, just, you know, allergies. Oof.
今年花粉四处弥漫
It is a heavy pollen year.
都上新闻了
It was on the news.
倒香槟啦
Here comes the bubbly.
倒吧  就像世界末日来了一样
Pour like there's no tomorrow.
你就要夺回你的丈夫了
You are getting your husband back.
我好开心啊
I'm so happy.
当然我也为艾普尔感到难过
Of course, I feel bad for April.
为什么  早知今日何必当初
Why? She should've known what was coming.
这就是电影的标准结局:
This is how the movie always ends:
男人回到妻子身边
the man slinks back to his wife,
狐狸精独自买醉
and the whore ends up drunk and alone.
我现在有四个孩子
Actually, now that I got four kids,
听起来没那么糟
it doesn't sound so bad.
我在想下周带艾普尔去餐厅
I was thinking of taking April to a restaurant next week.
你懂的  去给她打气
You know, to cheer her up.
贝丝·安  战争结束了
Beth Ann, the war is over.
你赢了  让敌人在失败中蹒跚吧
You won. Let the enemy limp away in defeat.
过去几周艾普尔和我变得很亲密
April and I grew very close these last few weeks.
这是真正的友谊
It's a true friendship.
她以为你的名字是希拉
She thinks your name is Sheila.
我承认  这很复杂...
I admit, it's a complicated...
宝贝  怎么了
Honey! What's wrong?
艾普尔在我的车道上
April is in my driveway.
我去
Shit.
她来这干嘛
What is she doing here?
我他妈怎么知道
Why the fuck should I know?
我们不能开门
We can't open the door.
应该避免不了了
I think we're gonna have to.
我觉得她看到我了
I think she saw me.
你得假装是我
You have to be me.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
拜托  我求你了
Please. I'm begging.
好吧
Fine.
我勒个去
Christ on a cracker.
别讲脏话
Don't swear.
友善一点
And be nice.
需要帮忙吗
May I help you?
你是罗伯特·斯坦顿太太吗
Are you Mrs. Robert Stanton?
是的
Yes.
请问你是谁  可以告诉我吗
And who might you be, pray tell?
我是艾普尔
I'm April.
我是格伦代尔的詹森餐厅的一名服务员
I'm... a-a waitress at Jansen's Diner in Glendale.
你丈夫是我的常客之一
Your husband is one of my regulars.
是吗
Is he?
是的
Yes.
我不是有意催你的  亲爱的
I don't mean to rush you, dear,
但我有窗帘要镶边  烤箱里还烤着面包
but I have curtains to hem and croutons in the oven.
好的  我只是想过来告诉你
Yes, I just wanted to come by to say
你丈夫吃饭时把外套落在餐厅了
that I think your husband might have left his coat at the diner.
饶了我吧
Well, mercy me.
我不确定是不是他的  但是...
I-I'm not even sure if it's his, but...
如果你不介意的话请告诉他我来过
if you wouldn't mind just telling him that I stopped by
然后让他给我打电话
and asking him to call me.
他知道你的号码...[意大利人口音]
He knows your number...
号码
number?
打给餐厅
At the diner.
他可以打给餐厅找我
He could just give me a call at the diner.
我会转告的
I'll tell him.
-再见吧  -再见
- Bye now. - Goodbye.
我从来没说过"饶了我吧"
I have never said "Mercy me."
但是你确实会自己烤面包
But you do bake your own croutons.
不敢相信艾普尔真的来我家了
I can't believe April actually came to the house.
不得不说  她挺厉害的
Got to say, I'm impressed.
那逼可不会轻易认输
That tramp, she ain't going down without a fight.
我这逼也不会
Well, this tramp isn't either.
你懂我意思
You know what I mean.
我十分钟后就得出发
I have to leave in ten minutes,
我完全不知道该穿什么
and I have got absolutely no idea what to wear.
你真可爱
You're so cute,
去和新男友吃个晚餐这么激动
all aflutter over your dinner with your new beau.
这个粉色会不会太基了
Is this pastel too gay?
你有见过不基的粉色吗
Have you ever seen a straight pastel?
你能放下报纸来帮帮我吗
Will you please put the paper down and help me?
我打算给你找个好地方住
I'm trying to find a nice place for you to live.
桑福德帕姆斯的公寓房间怎么样
Oh, what about a condo at Sanford Palms?
桑福德帕姆斯
Sanford Palms?
那地方离这里就五个街区
That's only about five blocks away from here.
我还是想和你共度电影之夜
Well, I still want us to have our movie nights.
这样你喝了鸡尾酒就不用开车回家啦
You wouldn't have to drive home after cocktails.
我们的朋友会鄙视我们的
Our friends are going to despise us.
为什么
Why?
当人们分手时
When people split up,
他们喜欢怨恨和发怒
they prefer venom and fireworks,
哭闹和指责
tears and accusations.
太小孩子气了
So childish and petty.
-再说我们上周已经这样做过了  -也对
- Besides, we did that last week. - Right.
我把范围缩小到了这两件
I've narrowed it down to these two.
你更喜欢哪件
Which do you prefer?
亚麻的那件
The linen.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你干嘛在意穿什么
Why do you care which suit?
要不了多久就要脱掉
How long is it gonna be on, really?
我是个品行端正的女孩儿  真的[出自电影《窈窕淑女》]
Oi! I'm a good girl, I am.
我只会让给我买了龙虾的先生碰我
I don't let no gentleman touch me what ain't bought me lobster first.
是汤米来了
Oh, that's Tommy.
跟他说话别学伊莉莎
Don't do Eliza for him.
他理解不了这梗
He won't understand the reference,
他会以为你中风了
and he'll think you're having a stroke.
没错  年轻一代人失去了很多幽默感
Yes. Much humor is lost on the younger generation.
裤子
Trousers!
汤米  快进来
Tommy. Come in.
格罗夫先生去哪儿了
Where's Mr. Grove?
他今晚有约会
He has a date tonight.
跟男人吗
With a guy?
是的
Yes.
我虽然失去了丈夫  但却收获了一个"基蜜"
I've lost a husband, but I've gained a gay sidekick.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
因为现在...
Because now...
我们再亲热就不用躲躲藏藏的了
we don't have to hide when we do this.
我感觉到有奇怪的东西在顶着我
I'm feeling something interesting.
那能怪我吗
Can you blame me?
我不是说你的下面  是这里
Not down there-- up here.
这是送给我的吗
Is this for me?
我本来想留到晚餐后再送给你的
I was saving that for after dinner.
你能再等一会儿吗
Do you think you can wait?
真是个好问题
What a question.
当然等不及啦
Of course not.
太美了
It's stunning.
你的品味提升了不少
Your taste is improving.
像你这样的女人值得拥有最好的
A woman like you deserves the best.
我希望你能明白  我可以给予你最好的
And I-I want you to see that I can give that to you.
汤米
Tommy!
他还没走吗
He hasn't left yet?
谢天谢地我逮着你了
Thank God I caught you.
我需要外人对我的服装发表下看法
I need fresh eyes on an outfit.
萨蒙妮更喜欢亚麻布的这件
Uh, Simone prefers the linen,
但我觉得海军蓝的这件更显瘦
but I think the navy's more slimming.
你觉得呢
Thoughts?
你本来就不胖啊
Y-You're not fat.
没错  作为直男  我的确算是很瘦了
Yes. As a straight man, I am boyishly slim.
但作为基佬  我还是再瘦一点比较好  所以...
However, as a homo, I could afford to lose a few. So...
瞧瞧汤米送了我什么礼物
See what Tommy gave me.
天呐  瞧瞧
Hark at you.
戴蒙德·吉姆·布雷迪手段
Diamond Jim Brady Bunch.
总之  该选哪件
Anyway, which one?
随便选一件吧
Just pick one.
海军蓝
Navy.
那就海军蓝了  谢谢
Navy it is. Thank you.
我很抱歉打扰你们
I'm terribly sorry to interrupt,
但你们也知道
but, as you know,
要出柜  选对衣服是极其重要的
it's very important to get the costume right when you're coming out.
我们不在乎你出不出柜  只要你出门就行
We don't care if you come out, just as long as you get out.
稍微暗示下我自然会懂的  萨蒙妮
I can always take a subtle hint, Simone.
或许有一天  你能学会这点
Perhaps, one day, you'll give me one.
跟赫克托说  如果他不给我做婚礼发型
Oh, tell Hector you won't sleep with him
你就不跟他上床
unless he does my hair for the wedding!
没问题  再见
You got it! Goodbye!
你的婚姻真是有趣极了
You have a very interesting marriage.
希拉
Sheila.
你来这里干什么
Um, what are you doing here?
昨天的见面被迫中断了  所以我...
Our visit was cut short yesterday, so I just...
现在不是时候  我觉得有点不舒服
Now's not really a good time; I'm feeling under the weather.
你想让我替你去药店买药吗
Do you want me to run to the drugstore for you?
不  不用  我只需要...
Oh, no, no. I just...
服用几片阿司匹林就好了
need a couple of aspirin.
坐下  我来帮你拿
Sit. I'll get them for you.
不必麻烦你的
Oh, you don't have to do that.
没事的
It's no trouble.
再说  我还有好消息要告诉你
Besides, I have some good news.
那很好啊
That's nice.
我倒是需要听听好消息
I could use some.
我给你找到一个好对象
I've found you a man.
他叫埃尔顿·拉辛格
His name's Eldon Ratzinger.
埃尔顿·拉辛格
Eldon Ratzinger.
他是我相熟的屠夫  人很好
He's my butcher. Very nice.
虽说人有点矮
On the short side,
但如果你穿平底鞋其实也注意不到
but you wouldn't notice if you're wearing flats.
谢谢  但是...
Thanks, but...
我近期以内都不想再恋爱了
I can't meet anyone for a while.
如果你坐在家里闷闷不乐  是忘不了罗伯的
You won't forget about Rob if you sit around pouting.
相信我  我短时间内都不可能忘掉罗伯
Trust me, I won't be forgetting about Rob anytime soon.
你必须克服对有妇之夫的痴迷
You've got to get over this obsession with another woman's husband.
你最后只会落得愤怒  悲伤的下场
You're going to end up angry and sad.
你说得很对
You are right about that.
其实  罗伯留下给我的并不只有花
You know, flowers aren't the only thing that Rob left me with.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
希拉  你受伤了吗
Sheila, are you hurt?
是的
Yes.
-没错  我伤得很重  -我去给你拿绷带
-Yes, I am. - Let me get you a bandage.
我来帮你拿  我的贵妇
Let me get that for you, my lady.
我的另外一位贵妇
And my other lady.
你可真有绅士风度
How chivalrous of you.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了
All right.
要我来开会儿车吗
You want me to drive for a bit?
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是对剧本的事感到很紧张
I think I'm just nervous about the script, you know?
你介意我们停一下  让我给拉马尔打个电话吗
Actually, do you guys mind if we pull off so I can call Lamar?
那可以让你不再把方向盘当邦哥鼓来敲打吗
Will that stop you from playing the steering wheel like a bongo drum?
几乎绝对可以
Almost definitely.
那你就这么做吧
Then by all means.
好极了  就在前面停车
Okay, great. Here we go.
好极了
Oh, great.
不知道这里有没有厕所
I wonder if they have a bathroom.
我们可以去便利店问问
Uh, we can ask inside the mini-mart.
你想要什么吗
Do you want anything?
薯片
Uh, potato chips.
巧克力奶
And chocolate milk.
如果有的话  再买些虫形软糖
And gummy worms, if they have 'em.
你是12岁的小孩吗
What are you, 12?
我知道你是  但我呢
I know you are, but what am I?
我一定会把这事告诉那些多角恋朋友的
The polyamorists will hear about this.
操
Fuck!
该死  该死  该死
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
坏消息  伊莱
Bad news, Eli!
没有虫形软糖了
They were out of worms.
不要啊
No.
所以我给你买了小熊软糖
So I got you bears.
谢谢
Thank you.
你开后备箱做什么
What are you doing in the trunk?
我在找我的棒球帽
Uh, looking for my baseball cap.
这样啊  那帽子在哪儿呢
Ah. So, where is it?
我忘记把它装包了
Forgot to pack it.
笨伊莱
Fuckin' Eli.
好了
All right.
我们出发吧
Let's hit the road.
亲爱的  你今早能否替我照看下画廊呢
Darling, is there any chance you can watch the gallery for me this morning?
你要去哪儿
Where will you be?
我有一个预约
Uh, I have an appointment.
这样啊
Oh.
这预约和你的新男朋友赫克托有关吗
And would this appointment involve your new boyfriend Hector?
他也许会一起来  没错
He may tag along, yes.
瞧你那小样  骄傲的同志男人
Look at you, proud gay man.
你知道我会全心全力支持你
You know I'd do anything to support you.
其实也就是取消我的健身房私教课
Short of canceling my training session at the gym.
你不也是一副同志男人[快乐的人]的模样吗
Are you sure you'renot a gay man?
娜奥米
Naomi.
我以为我们约好在俱乐部见面的
I thought we were meeting at the club.
你永远不知道谁会在偷听
You never know who's eavesdropping there.
而我将要说的  只能说给你的耳朵听
And what I have to say is for your ears only.
你好啊  娜奥米
Hello, Naomi.
我的耳朵和我正准备离开
My ears and I were just leaving.
不劳您大驾了
Thank you.
你看起来很不安啊
You seem upset.
你还记得我跟你说汤米在隐瞒些什么事吗
Remember when I told you that Tommy was hiding something?
我知道他的秘密了
I know his secret.
是吗
You do?
他在吸毒
He's on drugs.
谢天谢地啊
Oh, thank God.
你终于弄明白了
That you finally figured it out.
只有这样才能说得通...整天神神秘秘
It's the only thing that makes sense-- the secrecy,
午夜才回家  还给卧室门上锁
the long hours, the lock on his bedroom door.
更别提不见踪影的钱了
Not to mention the missing money.
什么钱
What money?
他把他的储蓄债券兑现了
He cashed in his savings bond.
他18岁成年后  这笔钱就归他所有
They became his when he turned 18.
我本不该知道这事的
And I'm not supposed to know,
不过我在银行的朋友偷偷告诉我了
but my friend at the bank tipped me off.
我问你  萨蒙妮
I ask you, Simone,
他买什么需要花一万块
what else could he have bought that cost $10,000?
他花了一万吗
He spent $10,000?
我就知道你会理解我的
I knew you'd understand.
你真是个知心朋友
You're such a good friend.
我知道我们曾经闹过不和
I know we've had our squabbles.
但是在这样的危机面前
But in a crisis like this,
我只有和你才可以倾诉倾诉了
there is no one else I can turn to.
只有我吗
No one?
你觉得他在吸什么毒
What do you think he's doing?
海洛因吗
Heroin?
我们可是在说汤米
This is Tommy we're talking about.
我才不相信他会去吸海洛因
I seriously doubt he's on heroin.
哎呀  这胸针真漂亮
What? That's a beautiful brooch.
是你新买的吗
Is it new?
不过再仔细想想  他确实有可能是在吸海洛因
Then again, it could be heroin.
崖畔度假酒店
我们到啦
All right.
快看这地方  可真不错
Oh, look at this place. It's cute.
天
Oh, man.
他们为什么要拦下每辆车啊
Why are they stopping everyone?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
居然有这么多车
Look at all these cars.
谁能想到多角恋这么流行呢
Who knew polyamory was so popular?
我的天
Oh, my God.
副总统彭斯今晚将在这里讲话
Vice President Pence is speaking here tonight.
在一个多角恋研讨会上吗
At a polyamory seminar?
-那可真令人意外  -好奇怪的选择
- That's surprising. - Odd choice.
不是
No.
他的活动是在酒店的另一间宴会厅
He's in a different ballroom.
他将与"当地共和党人士"交谈
He's talking to "Local Republicans."
原来他们拦车是因为这个
Well, that's the reason for the holdup.
安保加强了
It's extra security.
安保啊...
Oh, security...
他们在逐个开后备箱检查
They're opening people's trunks.
那要等好久了
That's gonna take forever.
你猜怎么着  二位
You know what, guys?
我们...我们需要掉个头
We-we, we need to turn around.
-你说什么  -没错
- What? - Yeah.
-为什么啊  -我得...我得去尿尿
- Why? - Uh... I-I got to, I got to pee, guys.
实在对不起
I'm so sorry.
-我真的...  -亲爱的  我刚才是开玩笑的
- I just... - No, honey, I was kidding.
酒店就在前面
The hotel is just up the street.
-我们很快就能到那...  -不行
- We'll be there in, like... - Nope.
不行  "大坝"就要泄了  我们这就...
Can't do it. Dam's gonna burst. Here-here we go...
别这样  亲爱的  慢着  你在干什么
No, honey, wait, what are you doing?
你到底在干什么
What are you doing?
我在努力调头
Oh! I'm flipping a bitch.
等下  伊莱  你搞什么...
Wait-- Eli, what...
你不能在这进行U形转弯啊
You can't make a U-turn here.
现在更像是一个三点转向了
Yeah, well, now it's turning into a bit more of a three-point thing.
-伊莱...  -伊莱  不要这样
- Eli... - Eli, no!
或是四点转向
Or four.
伊莱  我的天呐
Eli! Oh, my God!
我的神呐
Oh, my God.
伊莱  你到底在干嘛啊
Eli, what are you doing?
他们会把我们当作恐怖分子之类的了
They're gonna think that we're terrorists or something.
现在是五点转向了
Five.
看到了吗  多么流畅的驾驶技术
See that? Smooth sailing.
-你他妈的疯了吗  天...  -流畅的驾驶
- Have you lost your fucking mind? Jesus... - Smooth sailing.
伊莱  开慢点
Eli, slow down!
你要把我们都害死的
You're gonna get us all killed.
各位  都淡定点  好吗
Oh, wha-- everyone, just calm down, okay?
前面不远处有家塔可钟餐厅
There's a Taco Bell a couple miles down the road.
我们就停在那里  一切都会没事的
Right? We'll stop there, it's gonna be fine.
好吗  一切都会没事的
All right? Everything is gonna be fine.
怎么了
What?
停车  现在就停下
Stop the car. Now.
好吧
All right.
你干什么...你为什么要开后备箱啊
What-- Why are you opening the trunk?
因为我想看看里面都有什么
Because I want to know what's in there.
泰勒
Taylor!
糟了
Shit.
伊莱  你的鼻子
Eli, your nose.
操
Fuck.
等下
Wait.
我的天呐  伊莱
Oh, my God. Eli.
我...我知道这看起来很糟糕
I-I know that it looks bad.
坐回车里  我们回家
Get in the car. We're going home.
那...那度假怎么办呢
W-What about the retreat?
去他妈的度假
Oh, fuck the retreat.
她怀孕了  天呐
Pregnant? Jesus.
她不仅是个淫妇  还是个愚蠢的淫妇
She's not only a tramp, she's a stupid tramp.
-我现在不想喝酒  -亲爱的
- I don't want to drink right now. - Oh, honey.
这都是我要喝的  你的生活让我窒息
This is all for me. I find your life very stressful.
至少我们现在知道艾普尔为什么这么急切地想联系罗伯了
At least we know why April was so desperate to speak to Rob.
你觉得他会有什么反应
How do you think he'll react?
我觉得他会很激动的
I think he will be thrilled.
真的吗
Really?
罗伯以前很喜欢当爸爸的感觉
Rob loved being a father.
当我们失去艾米莉的时候  这是我们女儿的名字
When we lost Emily-- that was our daughter's name...
这名字很美
That's a beautiful name.
他无法接受我们失去了艾米莉
When we lost Emily, he couldn't accept it.
罗伯求我再生一个孩子
Rob begged me to have another child.
那你为什么没生
Why didn't you?
我们尝试了很多次  但是
We tried and tried, but...
你们考虑过领养吗
Did you ever think about adoption?
罗伯说他不想养别的男人的孩子
Rob said he didn't want to raise another man's baby.
他想要一个自己的孩子
He wanted a child of his own.
现在他就要有一个了
And now he's going to get one.
老天  我真讨厌这个男人
God, I hate this guy.
别这么说  他还是我的丈夫
please, he's still my husband.
我现在该怎么办
What do I do now?
摊牌
Come clean.
告诉他外遇和孩子的事情你都知道
Tell him you know about the affair, and the baby.
-不  -是时候把一切都摊开来说了
- No.- It's time to put it all on the table.
这会有用吗
But how will that help?
这能逼他做出选择
It will force him to make a choice.
选你还是她
You or her.
如果...他没有选我怎么办
What if... he doesn't choose me?
那你就能终于和我一样
Well, then you'll finally hate the fucking bastard
痛恨这混蛋了
just as much as I do.
我不会的  这就是问题所在
No, I won't. That's the problem.
听着  我不知道他会怎么做
Look, I don't know what he's gonna do.
也许他会选你
Maybe he'll choose you.
但不管是什么结果
But whatever happens,
你难道还没受够这些谎言吗
aren't you done with all the lies?
队员们  快跑  小心
Okay, team, let's go. Heads up!
防守  球场北侧
Defense, north side of the field.
进攻  南侧  动起来...
Offense, south side. Let's go...
你来这里干吗
Hey. What are you doing here?
你为什么没告诉我那些钻石是真的
Why didn't you tell me these diamonds were real?
它们当然是真的了  我以为你知道的
Yea-- of course they're real. I thought you knew that.
但我不知道  拿回去
Well, I didn't. Take this back.
不  我为什么要拿回来
No. Why would I do that?
银行告诉你妈妈说你卖了一份债券
The bank told your mother you sold a bond.
她现在觉得你在吸毒
She now thinks you're on drugs,
知道你把钱花在了这上面
and knowing what you spent on this,
我在想她有可能是对的
I'm wondering if she's right.
-我不会收的  -汤米
- I'm not taking it back. - Tommy.
我应该可以为我心爱的女人买钻石
I should be able to buy diamonds for the woman I love.
放松  我不指望你也这么说
Relax. I don't expect you to say it back.
我给你钻石是为了让你知道我不是什么
I gave you that so you'd see that I'm not just some kid
配不上你的小屁孩
who can't play in your league.
钻石是真的  因为我对你的感情是真的
The diamonds are real because my feelings are.
你知道我喜欢你
You know I adore you,
但是我不觉得我们能拥有正常的感情
but I just don't see how we can have that kind of relationship.
因为会有风言风语吗
Because of what people would say?
-他们会很粗鲁  -所以卡尔跟男人约会
- They'd be brutal. - So, you're not embarrassed
你不感到丢人  而我却让你觉得丢人了
that Karl dates men, but you are embarrassed by me?
我一点也不觉得丢人
I am not embarrassed at all.
我的天
Oh, dear God.
汤米  你女朋友是谁啊
Hey, Tommy! Who's your girlfriend?
我不能留在这了
I-I can't stay here.
-给  求你拿着吧  -不
- Here, take this, please.- No.
这是属于你的  爱你我并不羞愧
It's yours. I'm not ashamed to love you.
-泰勒  -闭嘴
- Taylor... - Don't.
现在谁也别说话
I need for no one to speak right now.
多久了
How long?
什么
Sorry?
你复吸有多久了
How long have you been using again?
没有很久
Not that long.
-差不多是在...  -别告诉我
- I mean, it started... - Don't tell me.
我不想知道我忽视了这些迹象有多久
I don't want to know how long I missed the signs.
也不想知道这事在我眼皮子底下
How long this has been happening
进行了多久
right in front of my own stupid face.
亲爱的  求你了  你...
Babe, please, you...
闭嘴
You-- shut up.
我之前被分心了
I was distracted before.
我现在可是睁大了双眼
You'd better believe my eyes are wide fucking open now.
喂
Hello?
汤米在贩毒
Tommy's dealing drugs.
什么
What?
凯·兰道的儿子布拉德利
Kay Randall's son Bradley
今天看到他...
saw him today...
跟一个客户在一起！
with a customer!
客户
A customer?
他看到他在体育课的时候
He saw him making a deal in the middle of P.E.
跟一个戴着墨镜的恶心中年女人
with some seedy, middle-aged woman
-做交易  -中年
- in dark glasses. - Middle-aged?
总之
Anyway,
你有螺丝刀吗
do you have a screwdriver?
我要闯进汤米的房间里去
I want to break into Tommy's room.
为什么  他肯定没把毒品藏在屋里
Why? I'm sure he doesn't keep drugs in there.
也许没有  但至少我可以看看他的日记
Maybe not, but at least I could read his journal.
他的日记
His journal?
我好像找到了
I think I found one.
你什么意思  他有写日记的习惯吗
W-Well, what do you mean, he keeps a journal?
我得挂了
I-I have to go.
娜奥米
Naomi.
- 娜奥米  - 在这里
- Naomi? - Up here!
娜奥米
Naomi.
你来了真好  你可帮我找
I'm so glad you're here. You can help me look.
我只是来阻止你做蠢事的
I am only here to stop you from making an awful mistake.
如果汤米发现你读过他的日记
If Tommy finds out you read his journal,
你可能会永远失去他
you could lose him forever.
他不会发现的  他要一直训练到六点
He won't find out. He's at track until 6:00.
你把他房间弄这么乱  来不及收拾的
You trashed his room. You won't have time to clean it up.
而且日记也不一定在这
And the journal may not even be here.
找到了
Found it.
萨蒙妮
Simone.
艾米10岁的时候我看过她的日记
When Amy was ten, I read her diary.
之后一年她都没跟我说过话
She didn't speak to me for a year.
-给我  -如果她当时是汤米现在这个年纪的话
- Hand it over.- If she had been Tommy's age,
她就直接搬出去了
she'd have moved out.
你真的愿意冒这个风险  就为了偷看
Do you really want to risk that, just to get an intrusive look
汤米最私密的想法和...
at Tommy's most private thoughts and...
-老天爷啊  -怎么了
- Jesus Christ. - What?
没什么
Nothing!
日记给我
Give me that.
作为你的朋友  我求求你  别看
As your friend, I am begging you, don't read that.
你为什么这么激动
Why are you so emotional?
卡尔是同性恋
Karl is gay.
-什么  -他跟男人睡觉
- What? - He sleeps with men.
我们能不能关注一下我的问题
can we just focus on my problems for a moment?
怪不得你最近这么心烦意乱
No wonder you're so distraught.
我本想告诉你
I mean, I wanted to tell you,
但我转念一想  "娜奥米有自己的麻烦
but then I thought, "No, Naomi has her own problems.
她不需要听我的俗气闹剧"
She doesn't want to hear my tawdry tale."
但我想听
Oh, but I do.
你是说
You mean to tell me
上次我在旅馆看到卡尔的车时
that when I saw Karl's car at the motel,
他和一个男人在一起
he was there with a man?
我得来杯酒才能接着说
I can't talk about this without a drink.
也许我们可以下楼
Maybe we could go downstairs and,
开一瓶
you know, open up a bottle?
当然  但你怎么发现的
Of course. But how did you find out?
你抓到他和情人的现行了
Did you catch him with one of his lovers?
不  是旺达  你说得对
No, it was Wanda. You were right.
她鄙视我
She despises me.
-她发现的  -你们在我房间干什么
- She found out... - What are you doing in my room?
那是我的日记吗
Is that my journal?
她刚找到
Uh, she just found it,
但还没有读
but she hasn't read it yet.
对不起  汤米
I'm so sorry, Tommy.
我只想确保你没有吸毒
I just wanted to make sure that you weren't doing drugs.
所以你就闯进我的房间
So you broke into my room?
谁让你最近都那么疏远我
Well, you've been so distant lately.
格罗夫太太  如果你不介意
Mrs. Grove, if you wouldn't mind...
对  我该走了  因为这事和我完全无关
Yes, I should go, as this doesn't involve me at all.
天哪  妈
Jesus. Mom...
你在找这些
You looking for these?
太好了  你找到了  谢谢
Oh, good, you found them. Thank you.
你们谈得怎么样
How'd it go in there?
刚告诉我妈  我打算
Eh, just told Mom that I'm gonna
再兑现一张债券  暑假去欧洲徒步旅行
cash in another bond so I can hike through Europe this summer.
她很愧疚闯进了我的房间  同意了
She felt so guilty about breaking into my room that she agreed.
你把局势转化成了利己的形势
You turned the situation to your advantage.
真有你的
Good for you.
我毕业典礼后两天出发去巴黎
I, uh, leave for Paris two days after graduation.
想一起来吗
Care to join me?
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我们不用一起走
We don't have to leave at the same time.
我先去  然后你度个假
I'll go first, then you take a vacation
和我在欧洲见
and meet me there.
没人会知道我们是一起去玩
No one's gonna know that we're together.
你妈在看我们
Your mother's watching.
所以我们必须去旅游
That is why we need to do this.
在这总会有人在看我们
Someone is always watching us here.
我们永远不知道咱俩是否能成  除非我们远离
We will never know who we can be as a couple until we get away
我妈  你的朋友们
from my mom, your friends,
和其他那些你怕他们对你有看法的人
and everyone else whose opinions you're scared of.
我能考虑一下吗
Can I think about it?
当然
Sure.
瞧瞧这丰盛的
Look at this.
有人大费周章啊
Someone went to a lot of trouble.
不算什么
Oh, not so much.
我就放了一些花  摆了上好的银器
I just put out a few flowers, and the good silver,
和你妈妈给我们买的蜡烛
and the candlesticks your mother bought us.
你想饭前来杯迈泰鸡尾酒吗
Would you like a mai tai before dinner?
你还调了迈泰鸡尾酒
You made mai tais?
等等  你是不是把车撞了
Hold it. Did you wreck the car?
你怎么会这么想
Why would you think that?
只有发生了坏事你才会给我调迈泰鸡尾酒
You only make mai tais before giving me bad news.
别傻了
That's silly.
喝你的迈泰鸡尾酒
Now drink your mai tai.
你要去哪呢
Where do you think you're going?
-楼上  -你一个人不行
- Upstairs. - Not alone, you're not.
事实上  接下去这么做
In fact, this is what's gonna happen right now.
咱俩在这屋子里逛一圈
You and I are gonna take a tour of this house,
你把所有藏毒的地方都告诉我
and you're gonna show me where you've been hiding your stash.
-我没藏毒  我就是  -而且伊莱
- There's no stash. I just... - And you know what, Eli,
把你的行李放下
put all that shit down,
因为你不必把东西整理出来
because you have absolutely no reason to unpack.
明天一早你就去戒毒所
You're going to rehab first thing in the morning.
你在逗我吗  戒毒所
Are you kidding? Rehab?
-别这样  -你的钱包手机都给我
- Come on. - I want your wallet. And your phone.
我不准你花钱了
You are cut off.
不给现金  卡  不准用贝宝或Venmo
No cash, no cards, no PayPal, no Venmo.
明白吗
Do you understand?
我明白你为什么不开心
You know, I understand why you're upset,
-但你也不用在洁德面前羞辱我  -错
- but you don't have to humiliate me in front of Jade, too. - Wrong.
你该被羞辱
You should be humiliated.
在上次事件以后
After what we went through last time,
一想到你又要让我们经历一次...
the idea that you would even put us through this again...
-伊莱  给我  -是拉马尔
- Eli, give it to me. - It's Lamar.
-他可以留言  -可能是
- He'll leave a message. - Just-- It could be
剧本的事呢  你就
about the script. Just...
就让我接这个电话吧
please let me take the call.
行
Fine.
待在我能看见你的地方
Stay where I can see you.
小泰
Yeah...Tay...
我想帮忙  告诉我要怎么帮你
I want to help. Just tell me what I can do.
多少
How much?
-陪着我就好  -好
- Just... be with me. - Yeah.
支持我  这事会很艰难
Back me up. This is gonna be really hard.
但这是唯一的办法
But it's the only way.
没问题  当然
Hey, you got it. Of course.
嗯  嗯  好的
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
拉马尔说什么
What did Lamar say?
他成功地让卖家竞标
He-he was able to start a bidding war...
并卖出了一个比我们预期高很多的价格
...and he sold it for a lot more than we expected.
高多少
How much more?
一百二
One-point-two.
-一百二  -万
- One-point-two? - Million.
一百二十万
1.2 million.
-天哪  -是啊
- Holy shit. - Yeah.
我的天
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
你说真的吗  我的天
Are you serious? Oh, my God.
-伊莱  恭喜  -天哪  谢谢  谢谢
- Eli, congratulations. - Oh, my God, thank you. Thank you.
-我的天  -太棒了
- Oh, my God. - Yes!
亲爱的  这真是好消息
Honey, this is such great news, okay?
你又东山再起了
Your career is back again.
所以你更加需要去戒毒所了
This is all the more reason to get you to rehab.
知道吗
You-you know what?
我觉得对我来说时机不合适
I-I don't, I don't think it's the best time for me,
现在不合适
right now.
哥们  你没有别的选择
Buddy... you don't really have a choice here.
我的剧本刚卖了一百二十万
I just sold a script for $1.2 million.
我觉得我的选择多得很
You know? I think I got a lot of fucking choices.
伊莱  我不会眼看着你杀了自己
Eli... I am not gonna stand by and watch you kill yourself.
天哪  别说了
Oh, God. Come on.
这不像上次  好吗
This is not like last time, all right?
-我现在状态很好  -伊莱
- I'm in a completely better place now. - Eli!
这没得商量
This is nonnegotiable.
-泰勒  -知道吗
- Taylor... - Do you know what...?
你太想控制我了  对吗
You're so fucking desperate to control me, aren't you?
-真是可悲  -够了  不  伊莱
- I mean, it's fucking pathetic! - Okay. No, Eli,
你是因为嗑了药才这么说的
this is the drugs talking.
-你知道的吧  -不  不是
- You know that, right? - No. No. No, it's not.
这是正常的我  我现在清醒得很
This is me, okay? I am clear as a fucking bell right now.
从现在起  我的决定我自己做主
And from now on... I make my own decisions.
好  伊莱  我给你个选择
Okay, Eli. Well, here's one for you:
要么你去戒毒所  要么我走
either you go to rehab, or I walk out that fucking door!
-慢着  慢着  -是吗
- Whoa. Hold on. Hold on. - Really?
-是的  -是吗  你就这么走掉
- Yeah. Oh, yeah. - Really? You just walk on out?
-如果你逼我  我会的  -好的  泰勒
- If you push me, yeah. - Okay. Well, Taylor,
我真的希望你不会走
you know, I really wish you wouldn't go.
但如果你想走  这是你的选择
But if you want to, that's your choice.
看  我永远不会逼你做任何事
See? I would never force you to do anything.
我们走  洁德
Come on, Jade.
洁德
Jade...
我觉得也许我们不该走
I-- I think maybe we shouldn't go.
-什么  -伊莱需要帮助
- You what? - Eli needs help.
我想帮助他最好的方式
I think maybe the best way to help him is to
就是留下来
stay here and-and, you know,
看着他
just keep an eye on him.
你选择他
You're choosing him.
我选择我们  我选择我们所有人
I'm choosing us. I'm choosing all of us.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
你们都去死吧
Fuck you both.
不敢相信你做了酥皮黄桃馅饼
I can't believe you made peach cobbler.
我知道这是你的最爱
I know it's your favorite.
你肯定中午就开始做了
You must've been cooking since noon.
我没那么早开始
I didn't start all that early.
谢谢你做的菜  今晚很棒
Well, thanks for this. It was a beautiful night.
不客气
You're welcome.
天
Aw, geez.
我就知道  有事情不对劲
I knew it. Something's going on.
罗伯特
Robert?
还叫我罗伯特  肯定是坏消息吧
And you're calling me Robert? Ah, this is gonna be bad, huh?
我们真的得谈谈
We definitely need to have a talk.
老天
Ah, boy.
首先
First...
我就想说
I just want to say...
我很爱你
...I love you so much.
更重要的是
And more importantly,
我爱我们  以及我们一起走过的日子
I love us. And the life we've had.
你吓到我了
You're starting to scare me.
我也吓到了
I'm scared, too.
怎么了  出什么事了
What's going on? What's wrong?
告诉我
Just tell me.
我一旦告诉你
Once I tell you...
一切都将不一样
...everything is going to be different.
我的天  你病了吗
Oh, my God. Are you sick?
是的
Yes.
我病了
I'm sick.
亲爱的  怎么了
Baby, what's wrong?
我得癌症了
I have cancer.
天啊  我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
天啊
Oh... oh, my God.
真漂亮的花
Oh, nice flowers.
是赫克托送的吗
Are they from Hector?
你以为我跟多少男人在交往
How many men do you think I'm juggling?
我很高兴我们中有人今天过得很开心
Oh, glad one of us is having a good day.
天  我看着就像浣熊
Oh, God, I look like a raccoon.
我不能告诉你我今天经历了什么
I cannot tell you what I've been through today.
你可以试试
I'm guessing you'll try.
你知道汤米送我的胸针吧
You know the pin Tommy gave me?
那钻石竟然是真的
Well, it turns out the diamonds were real.
娜奥米气死了
Naomi was furious,
因为他为了买胸针而兑现了他的储蓄债券
because he cashed in one of his savings bonds to buy it.
总之  她认定他在嗑药
Anyway, she decided he was on drugs.
她想去看她的日记
And that she had to read his journal...
格罗夫先生  有何贵干
Mr. Grove. How can I help you?
我之前和朋友在一起
Well, I was with my friend,
他在我背上发现了这个
and he-he spotted this thing on my back.
可能没什么
I mean, it's probably nothing,
但他建议我来看医生
but he-he suggested I see a doctor.
你来看我是正确的
You were right to come see me.
娜奥米没有发现让我松了口气
I am just relieved that Naomi didn't find out.
总之
Anyway...
在我走之前  汤米跑出来
before I left, Tommy ran out,
跟我说了件事  我得跟你谈谈
and said something that I definitely need to talk to you about.
天  我还要再喝点红酒吗
Oh, dear. Am I going to need more wine-- Oh!
该死
Damn it!
-严重吗  我看看  -别
- Oh, is it bad? Let me see... - No!
不用  抱歉  没有很深
No, no. No, no, sorry. Um, uh, it-it's not deep.
你能给我拿张创口贴吗
Can you just get me a Band-Aid?
当然
Of course.
所以汤米说了什么
Uh, uh, so, uh, what did Tommy say?
他暑假要去欧洲
Well, he's going to Europe for the summer,
他想我跟他一起去
and he wants me to join him.
我知道这听上去很疯狂
I know it sounds crazy,
但我想这也许不错  花时间跟他在一起
but I thought it might be nice to spend time with him...
不用偷偷摸摸  你觉得呢
and not have to sneak around. What do you think?
你应该去
You should go.
真的吗  这段时间很忙  艾米要办婚礼
Really? I mean, it's a hectic time, with Amy's wedding,
-还有画廊的事  -听着
- and the gallery... - Listen, listen.
我这辈子都在推迟
I have spent my entire life putting off things
我以为之后会有时间再做的事
that I thought there'd be time for later.
敞开的门不会永远敞开
Open doors don't stay open forever.
请你去吧
So please... go.
你不会有事吧
You'll be okay?
我会很开心的
I'll be delightful.
当然了
I'll bet.
看看那些花  赫克托肯定很浪漫
Judging from those flowers, Hector must be smitten.
是的
Yes.
*我尽力*
* I try *
你会战胜这病的  爱你的  赫克托
*但我不会忘记*
* But there's no forgetting *
*当夜幕降临*
* When evening appears *
*我叹气*
* I sigh *
*但我不会后悔*
* But there's no regretting *
*纵使我泪流满面*
* In spite of my tears *
*恶魔在你心中*
* The devil was in your heart *
*但你眼里是天堂*
* But heaven was in your eyes *
*你告诉我*
* The night that you told me *
*善意谎言的那晚*
* All those little white lies *
*那些善意*
* All those little white *
*谎言*
* Lies. *